

PROFILE

Full Stack Web Developer and experienced Registered Nurse wanting to apply my web development and medical skills towards creating software that will allow health systems and organizations work together to improve the health outcomes of the communities they serve.

Within healthcare, nurses have the most interaction with patients and technology. I strongly feel that technology should create a positive influence on nursing productivity. In my desire to improve the quality of healthcare, I am committed to creating functional and useable software that will enhance patient care.

CONTACT

PHONE: (479) 461-7075

WEBSITE:

<u>Professional Portfolio</u> <u>gitHub profile</u>

EMAIL:

Jkfout1@gmail.com

HOBBIES

True Crime Podcast Listener Book Reader Watching local sport teams play

JENNIFER HARDEN

Full Stack Developer

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Boot Camp

February 2019 – August 2019 Experience with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, and Node.js

Oklahoma Wesleyan University

2014 - 2016

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Registered Nurse

WORK EXPERIENCE

Cerner - Senior Clinical Terminologist

August 2015–Present

Proprietary code standardization and project management

AseraCare – Nursing Supervisor

June 2014-August 2015

Managed nurses for Hospice Call Center, scheduling, project management, software testing and debugging

Golden Living - Business System Analyst 3/Clinical IT Nurse

January 2013-June 2014

Homecare Homebase specialist resource for nurses, data specialist to help agencies to complete billing

SKILLS

